const level1 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What is the purpose of a job interview?",
        answer: "To showcase your qualifications and skills",
        options: [
            "To socialize with potential employers",
            "To test your knowledge of trivia",
            "To showcase your qualifications and skills"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How should you dress for a job interview?",
        answer: "Formal and professional",
        options: [
            "Casual and comfortable",
            "Formal and professional",
            "Loud and attention-grabbing"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What should you research about a company before an interview?",
        answer: "Their mission, values, and products/services",
        options: [
            "Their mission, values, and products/services",
            "Their social media activity",
            "Their employee's personal lives"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How soon after an interview should you send a thank-you note?",
        answer: "Within 24 hours",
        options: [
            "It's not necessary to send a thank-you note",
            "Within a week",
            "Within 24 hours"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the best way to answer the question: What is your greatest strength?",
        answer: "Mention a relevant professional strength and provide an example",
        options: [
            "Mention a relevant professional strength and provide an example",
            "Talk about a personal achievement",
            "Express your modesty and skip the question"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How should you handle a question about your weaknesses during an interview?",
        answer: "Mention a minor weakness and discuss how you are working to improve it in the question",
        options: [
            "Pretend you have no weaknesses",
            "Refuse to answer",
            "Mention a minor weakness and discuss how you are working to improve it in the question"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What is the purpose of a resume in the job application process?",
        answer: "Providing detailed information about qualifications and work history",
        options: [
            "Providing detailed information about qualifications and work history",
            "Sharing personal hobbies and interests",
            "Listing personal references"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the importance of body language during a job interview?",
        answer: "It can convey confidence, interest, and professionalism",
        options: [
            "It has no impact on the impression you make",
            "It can convey confidence, interest, and professionalism",
            "It's only relevant if you're applying for a job in acting or modelling"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How should you prepare for common interview questions?",
        answer: "Review common questions and practice thoughtful responses",
        options: [
            "Ignore them and answer spontaneously",
            "Review common questions and practice thoughtful responses",
            "Wing it not worrying to prepare for it"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "You've just entered the interview room and two people are waiting to interview you. What do you do first?",
        answer: "Shake their hands firmly, introduce yourself, and wait for them to direct you to a seat",
        options: [
            "Shake their hands firmly, introduce yourself, and wait for them to direct you to a seat",
            "Greet them with a smile and wait for them to offer you a seat",
            "Sit down and wait for them to speak"
        ]
    }
    
  ];

  const level2 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Of these options, what is the most important aspect of preparing for a job interview?",
        answer: "Researching the company",
        options: [
            "Choosing the right outfit",
            "Researching the company",
            "Memorizing your resume"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Effective communication during an interview involves:",
        answer: "Listening actively and responding thoughtfully",
        options: [
            "Speaking loudly and clearly",
            "Using technical jargon to demonstrate knowledge",
            "Listening actively and responding thoughtfully"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Which of the following is a hard skill?",
        answer: "Data Analysis",
        options: [
            "Data Analysis",
            "Teamwork",
            "Empathy"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "A key soft skill that employers often look for is:",
        answer: "Time management",
        options: [
            "Coding proficiency",
            "Time management",
            "Advanced mathematics"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "When presenting an international certification, it is important to:",
        answer: "Present the original document (or a copy if you do not have one)",
        options: [
            "Only show certifications recognized in your own country",
            "Translate it into the local language if necessary",
            "Present the original document (or a copy if you do not have one)"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "An out-of-country certification may be valuable because it shows:",
        answer: "Unique skills or perspectives gained abroad",
        options: [
            "The candidate's willingness to travel",
            "Unique skills or perspectives gained abroad",
            "Higher education standards than local certifications"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "When you are training your successor to your job, you should focus on:",
        answer: "Technical skills relevant to the job",
        options: [
            "Skills relevant to hobbies and community service",
            "Skills that are high in demand in the current job market",
            "Technical skills relevant to the job"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Retiring employees can prepare by:",
        answer: "Mentoring younger employees",
        options: [
            "Immediately stopping all professional development",
            "Mentoring younger employees",
            "Focusing only on financial planning"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "The Guhuza site for smart matching jobs is beneficial because it:",
        answer: "Matches skills with appropriate job opportunities",
        options: [
            "Matches skills with appropriate job opportunities",
            "Offers the highest-paying jobs",
            "Only lists jobs in the tech industry"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "For a successful career transition, it's important to:",
        answer: "Identify transferable skills and adapt them to new roles",
        options: [
            "Focus solely on past experiences",
            "Identify transferable skills and adapt them to new roles",
            "Ignore soft skills and focus on technical abilities"
        ]
    }
];

const level3 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What feature distinguishes Guhuza from other job-matching platforms?",
        answer: "Use of AI for smart skill matching",
        options: [
            "Use of AI for smart skill matching",
            "Specialization in high-salary jobs",
            "Focus on international job postings"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How does Guhuza assist new employees in finding suitable jobs?",
        answer: "Both a and b",
        options: [
            "By conducting live interviews right on Guhuza with the employer",
            "By alerting matched candidates of live interview opportunities",
            "Both a and b"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What is a key strategy for a successful job interview?",
        answer: "Demonstrating knowledge about the company",
        options: [
            "Discussing salary at the beginning",
            "Focusing on personal life stories",
            "Demonstrating knowledge about the company"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which is an example of a soft skill?",
        answer: "Negotiation",
        options: [
            "Negotiation",
            "Spreadsheet proficiency",
            "Machine operation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Why are transferable skills important in job interviews?",
        answer: "They can be applied to various roles and industries",
        options: [
            "They demonstrate specialized knowledge",
            "They are unique to each individual",
            "They can be applied to various roles and industries"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How should one present an out-of-country certification in an interview?",
        answer: "Both a and b",
        options: [
            "By explaining its relevance to the job",
            "By comparing it to local certifications",
            "Both a and b"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "An international certification can be beneficial because:",
        answer: "It may bring diverse perspectives",
        options: [
            "It guarantees a higher salary",
            "It may bring diverse perspectives",
            "It is always preferred by employers"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How can retiring individuals transfer their skills to a new opportunity?",
        answer: "By volunteering or consulting in their field of expertise",
        options: [
            "By starting a completely different career",
            "By volunteering or consulting in their field of expertise",
            "By ignoring past experiences"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Preparing for retirement should ideally involve:",
        answer: "Planning for the use of skills in post-retirement activities",
        options: [
            "Disengaging from all professional networks",
            "Focusing solely on financial aspects",
            "Planning for the use of skills in post-retirement activities"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Why should a candidate sign up with Guhuza?",
        answer: "For personalized job matching based on skills",
        options: [
            "To receive daily job alerts",
            "For personalized job matching based on skills",
            "For access to exclusive job listings"
        ]
    }
];
const level4 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Signing up with Guhuza can help you by:",
        answer: "Finding you job opportunities faster",
        options: [
            "Automatically updating your resume",
            "Providing insights into industry trends",
            "Finding you job opportunities faster"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Guhuza helps candidates in their job search by:",
        answer: "Identifying jobs that match their skill set and career goals",
        options: [
            "Limiting the number of applications they can send",
            "Identifying jobs that match their skill set and career goals",
            "Focusing on international positions only"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What happens if you are not available for an interview with Guhuza pings you?",
        answer: "Both a and b",
        options: [
            "Do not worry - there will be another opportunity soon",
            "Go in as soon as you are ready, even if it is later, as the employer may still be interviewing",
            "Both a and b"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "What advantage does getting an interview through Guhuza offer?",
        answer: "Interviews with top companies",
        options: [
            "Guaranteed job placement",
            "Interviews with top companies",
            "Feedback on interview performance"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "How can Guhuza improve your interview chances?",
        answer: "You will only be pinged for jobs that are matched to your background",
        options: [
            "You will only be pinged for jobs that are matched to your background",
            "By providing detailed company information",
            "By guaranteeing a second interview"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "After getting an interview through Guhuza, you can expect:",
        answer: "shorter interview process",
        options: [
            "An immediate job offer",
            "Insight into the company culture and expectations",
            "shorter interview process"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "The interview process with Guhuza is beneficial because:",
        answer: "It matches the candidate's skills with the job requirements",
        options: [
            "It includes a trial work period",
            "It is shorter than the industry standard",
            "It matches the candidate's skills with the job requirements"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the key benefit of securing an interview through Guhuza?",
        answer: "Getting a job faster",
        options: [
            "Getting a job faster",
            "Receiving a higher starting salary",
            "Access to hidden job markets"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Using Guhuza for job search can be beneficial because:",
        answer: "It offers a wide range of job types",
        options: [
            "It offers a wide range of job types",
            "It includes free resume-writing services",
            "It guarantees job satisfaction"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Guhuza's job matching algorithm is beneficial because it:",
        answer: "Tailors job searches to the candidate's experience",
        options: [
            "Focuses only on the most recent job listings",
            "Tailors job searches to the candidate's experience",
            "Considers personality traits in job matches"
        ]
    }
];
const level5 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Guhuza helps in preparing job seekers for interviews by:",
        answer: "Displaying the job description to the job seeker",
        options: [
            "Displaying the job description to the job seeker",
            "Offering virtual interview practice sessions",
            "Sending automatic reminders for interview dates"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "A benefit of Guhuza's job matching service is:",
        answer: "Reduced time in finding suitable job opportunities",
        options: [
            "Networking opportunities with other job seekers",
            "Reduced time in finding suitable job opportunities",
            "Regular job market analysis reports"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Guhuza enhances job search efficiency by:",
        answer: "Notifying job seekers based on user preferences",
        options: [
            "Organizing job fairs",
            "Notifying job seekers based on user preferences",
            "Offering weekend job search support"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How does Guhuza tailor its job recommendations?",
        answer: "According to experience and skills",
        options: [
            "According to experience and skills",
            "Based on previous job titles",
            "Solely on the education level"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Guhuza's user interface is designed to:",
        answer: "Simplify job search and application processes",
        options: [
            "Provide a gaming experience",
            "Simplify job search and application processes",
            "Offer social networking features"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Guhuza's job matching technology primarily benefits users by:",
        answer: "Matching them with roles that fit their skillset immediately",
        options: [
            "Reducing the need for cover letters",
            "Providing real-time job market trends",
            "Matching them with roles that fit their skillset immediately"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Where did Guhuza start?",
        answer: "Toronto, Canada",
        options: [
            "New York City, USA",
            "Mexico City, Mexico",
            "Toronto, Canada"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Guhuza distinguishes itself from other job platforms by?",
        answer: "Its user-friendly mobile application",
        options: [
            "Only listing jobs from Fortune 500 companies",
            "Offering a money-back guarantee if not hired",
            "Its user-friendly mobile application"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "What is the recommended length for a standard resume?",
        answer: "Two pages",
        options: [
            "One page",
            "Two pages",
            "Three pages"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following should be included in the (Skills) section of a resume?",
        answer: "Certifications",
        options: [
            "Hobbies",
            "Certifications",
            "Favorite movies"
        ]
    }
];

const level6 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "When listing work experience on a resume, what is the preferred order?",
        answer: "Most recent to oldest",
        options: [
            "Most recent to oldest",
            "Oldest to most recent",
            "Random order"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How should you begin your resume?",
        answer: "With a professional summary or objective statement",
        options: [
            "With a detailed personal story",
            "With a professional summary or objective statement",
            "With your most recent job title"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "When listing your work experience, what is most important?",
        answer: "The relevance of each job to the position you're applying for",
        options: [
            "The relevance of each job to the position you're applying for",
            "The duration of each job",
            "The prestigiousness of the company"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How should you format your educational background?",
        answer: "Only include relevant degrees or certifications",
        options: [
            "List every course you've ever taken",
            "Only include relevant degrees or certifications",
            "Focus on extracurricular activities"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What is the best way to showcase your skills?",
        answer: "Tailor your skills to match the job description",
        options: [
            "Tailor your skills to match the job description",
            "List as many skills as possible",
            "Focus on soft skills only"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How should achievements be presented in your resume?",
        answer: "Using specific examples and quantifiable results",
        options: [
            "As a simple list of all achievements",
            "In a separate document",
            "Using specific examples and quantifiable results"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "How should you handle gaps in your employment history?",
        answer: "Address them briefly and focus on what you learned during that time",
        options: [
            "Address them briefly and focus on what you learned during that time",
            "Ignore them and hope the employer doesn't notice",
            "Provide a detailed explanation for each gap"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What is the best way to format your resume?",
        answer: "A clean, professional layout with easy-to-read fonts",
        options: [
            "Using multiple colours and fonts to stand out",
            "A unique format for each job application",
            "A clean, professional layout with easy-to-read fonts"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Should you include references in your resume?",
        answer: "Only include references if specifically asked",
        options: [
            "Only include references if specifically asked",
            "Always include at least three references",
            "List all professional contacts you have"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "How important is it to customize your resume for each job application?",
        answer: "Very important; to tailor your resume to each job description",
        options: [
            "Not necessary; one resume fits all applications",
            "Very important; to tailor your resume to each job description",
            "Only change your personal statement for each application"
        ]
    }
];
const level7 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What Medium Should You Use to Send Your Thank-You Note?",
        answer: "Email",
        options: [
            "Email",
            "Handwritten letter",
            "Text message"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "What Should be Included in Your Thank-You Note?",
        answer: "A brief thank-you and reiteration of your interest",
        options: [
            "A summary of your qualifications",
            "A brief thank-you and reiteration of your interest",
            "Details of your salary expectations"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "If You Haven't Heard Back, How Long Should You Wait Before Following Up?",
        answer: "2 weeks",
        options: [
            "1 week",
            "3 days",
            "2 weeks"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How Should You Follow Up if You Haven't Received a Response?",
        answer: "Send a follow-up email",
        options: [
            "Send a follow-up email",
            "Call the interviewer directly",
            "Post a message on the company's social media page"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What Should You Avoid Doing While Waiting for a Response?",
        answer: "Continuously checking in with the employer",
        options: [
            "Preparing for other job opportunities",
            "Continuously checking in with the employer",
            "Reflecting on your interview performance"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "If You Receive a Rejection, How Should You Respond?",
        answer: "Thank the interviewer and express interest in future opportunities",
        options: [
            "Ask for detailed feedback",
            "Express disappointment and disagreement",
            "Thank the interviewer and express interest in future opportunities"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "When Networking Post-Interview, What is a Good Strategy?",
        answer: "Connect with the interviewer on LinkedIn",
        options: [
            "Connect with the interviewer on LinkedIn",
            "Send regular updates about your job search",
            "Ask for introductions to other professionals in the company"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How Well Did I Understand the Job Role?",
        answer: "Very well, I could explain it in detail",
        options: [
            "Somewhat, but some aspects were unclear",
            "Very well, I could explain it in detail",
            "Not very well, I need to research more"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Was I Able to Effectively Communicate My Skills and Experience?",
        answer: "Yes, I gave clear examples and related them to the role",
        options: [
            "No, I struggled to express my qualifications",
            "Partially, but I could have been more specific",
            "Yes, I gave clear examples and related them to the role"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "How Well Did I Answer the Behavioral Questions?",
        answer: "I provided specific examples and results",
        options: [
            "I answered, but my examples were not very relevant",
            "I provided specific examples and results",
            "I found it difficult to come up with examples"
        ]
    }
];

const level8 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Did I Ask Relevant and Insightful Questions About the Company and Role?",
        answer: "Yes, I asked detailed questions that showed my interest",
        options: [
            "No, I didn't ask any questions",
            "I asked a few questions but could have been more inquisitive",
            "Yes, I asked detailed questions that showed my interest"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How Confident Did I Feel During the Interview?",
        answer: "Very confident, I felt at ease",
        options: [
            "Very confident, I felt at ease",
            "Moderately confident, but I was nervous at times",
            "Not confident, I was very anxious"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Did I Research the Company Adequately Before the Interview?",
        answer: "Yes, I had comprehensive knowledge about the company",
        options: [
            "Somewhat, but I could have known more",
            "Yes, I had comprehensive knowledge about the company",
            "No, I needed to do more research"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How Well Did I Handle Unexpected Questions?",
        answer: "I adapted quickly and answered well",
        options: [
            "I managed, but my answers could have been better",
            "I adapted quickly and answered well",
            "I was thrown off and struggled to answer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What Was the Quality of My Closing Remarks?",
        answer: "Strong, I reiterated my interest and thanked the interviewer",
        options: [
            "Weak, I didn't summarize or thank the interviewer properly",
            "Adequate, but I could have been more impactful",
            "Strong, I reiterated my interest and thanked the interviewer"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How Do You Prioritize Your Work When You Have Multiple Deadlines?",
        answer: "I assess each task's urgency and importance and plan accordingly",
        options: [
            "I focus on the tasks I enjoy the most first",
            "I assess each task's urgency and importance and plan accordingly",
            "I work on whatever comes up first"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Describe a Time When You Had to Adjust Your Schedule at the Last Minute. How Did You Manage It?",
        answer: "I rescheduled less important tasks and focused on the urgent one",
        options: [
            "I rescheduled less important tasks and focused on the urgent one",
            "I asked for an extension on the deadline",
            "I often find it difficult to adjust to sudden changes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How Do You Handle Interruptions to Your Workday?",
        answer: "I assess the urgency of the interruption and then either address it or return to my original task",
        options: [
            "I get easily distracted but eventually return to my tasks",
            "I assess the urgency of the interruption and then either address it or return to my original task",
            "I stick to my planned tasks, ignoring interruptions"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "When Planning a Project, How Do You Organize Your Time?",
        answer: "I divide the project into smaller tasks and set deadlines for each",
        options: [
            "I divide the project into smaller tasks and set deadlines for each",
            "I usually start working on it and see where it goes",
            "I wait for inspiration or a deadline to get closer before starting"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "How Do You Ensure You Meet Deadlines?",
        answer: "I set earlier internal deadlines to ensure I'm always ahead",
        options: [
            "I work best under pressure, so I wait until the deadline is near",
            "I try my best but sometimes miss deadlines due to unforeseen circumstances",
            "I set earlier internal deadlines to ensure I'm always ahead"
        ]
    }
];

const level9 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Can You Give an Example of a Time Management Tool or Technique You Use?",
        answer: "I use digital tools like calendar apps and to-do lists",
        options: [
            "I keep everything in my head and rely on memory",
            "I don't usually use any specific tool or technique",
            "I use digital tools like calendar apps and to-do lists"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How Do You Balance Work and Personal Time?",
        answer: "I set clear boundaries between work and personal time",
        options: [
            "I often work late and on weekends",
            "I set clear boundaries between work and personal time",
            "I take work home often to stay on top of things"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Describe How You Handled Working on Multiple Projects Simultaneously",
        answer: "I delegate tasks when possible and prioritize based on deadlines",
        options: [
            "I delegate tasks when possible and prioritize based on deadlines",
            "I try to work on all projects a little each day",
            "I focus on one project at a time and ignore the others until I'm finished"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How Do You Stay Motivated and Productive When Working Remotely?",
        answer: "I maintain a regular schedule and set daily goals",
        options: [
            "I take frequent breaks to avoid burnout",
            "I work whenever I feel most productive, regardless of the time",
            "I maintain a regular schedule and set daily goals"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "How Do You Manage Communication with Your Team While Working Remotely?",
        answer: "I use a mix of communication tools and regularly check-in with team members",
        options: [
            "I prefer to communicate via email as it's more convenient",
            "I use a mix of communication tools and regularly check-in with team members",
            "I wait for others to reach out to me for updates"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What Tools Do You Use to Stay Organized and Meet Deadlines in a Remote Setting?",
        answer: "I use digital tools like task management software and calendars",
        options: [
            "I rely on memory and jot down notes occasionally",
            "I keep a physical planner or diary",
            "I use digital tools like task management software and calendars"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "How Do You Handle Distractions and Stay Focused While Working from Home?",
        answer: "I have a dedicated workspace and follow a strict routine",
        options: [
            "I work in short bursts between personal tasks",
            "I usually work with background noise like TV or music",
            "I have a dedicated workspace and follow a strict routine"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Describe Your Experience with Remote Collaboration Tools (e.g., Zoom, Slack)",
        answer: "I'm proficient with various collaboration tools and adapt to new ones quickly",
        options: [
            "I've used them occasionally but prefer face-to-face meetings",
            "I'm proficient with various collaboration tools and adapt to new ones quickly",
            "I find them complicated and prefer traditional methods of communication"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How Do You Ensure Clear and Effective Communication in a Virtual Team?",
        answer: "I regularly provide updates and encourage feedback for clarity",
        options: [
            "I regularly provide updates and encourage feedback for clarity",
            "I communicate only when necessary to avoid overwhelming team members",
            "I assume everyone is on the same page unless told otherwise"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "How Do You Balance Work-Life While Working Remotely?",
        answer: "I set clear boundaries between work hours and personal time",
        options: [
            "I work at any hour, blending work and personal life",
            "I often work late nights and weekends to stay on top",
            "I set clear boundaries between work hours and personal time"
        ]
    }
];

const level10 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "How Do You Handle the Lack of Physical Supervision in Remote Work?",
        answer: "I'm self-motivated and manage my tasks efficiently without supervision",
        options: [
            "I need regular check-ins to stay on track",
            "I'm self-motivated and manage my tasks efficiently without supervision",
            "I often struggle to stay focused without supervision"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How Would You Handle a Situation Where You Discovered a Coworker Acting Unethically?",
        answer: "Report it to a supervisor or relevant authority immediately",
        options: [
            "Report it to a supervisor or relevant authority immediately",
            "Confront the coworker directly and advise them to stop",
            "Ignore it as it's not my responsibility"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Have You Ever Faced a Conflict of Interest in Your Work? How Did You Handle It?",
        answer: "I disclosed it to my supervisor and recused myself from the situation",
        options: [
            "I have never experienced a conflict of interest",
            "I tried to balance both interests fairly",
            "I disclosed it to my supervisor and recused myself from the situation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Describe a Time When You Had to Uphold Confidentiality at Work",
        answer: "I always keep work-related information confidential, regardless of the situation",
        options: [
            "I don't usually worry about confidentiality",
            "I share confidential information only with trusted colleagues",
            "I always keep work-related information confidential, regardless of the situation"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What Would You Do If Asked to Perform a Task That You Believe Is Unethical?",
        answer: "Refuse to do it and explain my reasons to my supervisor",
        options: [
            "Refuse to do it and explain my reasons to my supervisor",
            "Do it, as it's important to follow instructions",
            "Consult with a colleague about what to do"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "How Do You Ensure Fairness and Equity in Your Decision-Making?",
        answer: "I treat everyone the same, regardless of their position",
        options: [
            "I make decisions based on personal relationships",
            "I treat everyone the same, regardless of their position",
            "I follow company policy strictly, even if it seems unfair"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "What Is Your Approach to Handling Company Resources?",
        answer: "I use them responsibly and only for work-related purposes",
        options: [
            "I believe company resources can be freely used as a perk of the job",
            "I occasionally use them for personal reasons if it doesn’t harm anyone",
            "I use them responsibly and only for work-related purposes"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "How Would You React If You Saw Someone Being Treated Unfairly in the Workplace?",
        answer: "I would report it to human resources or a supervisor",
        options: [
            "I would try to resolve the issue myself",
            "I would report it to human resources or a supervisor",
            "I wouldn't get involved as it might create conflict for me"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Can You Give an Example of How You Uphold Professional Ethics in Your Work?",
        answer: "I adhere to company policies and report any violations",
        options: [
            "I adhere to company policies and report any violations",
            "I follow ethics when it aligns with my personal beliefs",
            "Professional ethics are not my main concern, as long as the work gets done"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "How Do You Follow Up After Submitting a Job Application?",
        answer: "I send a polite email inquiring about the status after a week or two",
        options: [
            "I don't follow up; I wait for the employer to contact me",
            "I frequently call the office to ask if they have made a decision",
            "I send a polite email inquiring about the status after a week or two"
        ]
    }
];

const level11 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "What Do You Include in a Thank-You Note After an Interview?",
        answer: "A brief thank-you message and a recap of why I'm a good fit for the role",
        options: [
            "Just a simple thank-you message",
            "A detailed list of my qualifications and experiences",
            "A brief thank-you message and a recap of why I'm a good fit for the role"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "How Do You Address a Cover Letter When You Don't Know the Hiring Manager's Name?",
        answer: "I research to find the name or use 'Dear Hiring Manager'",
        options: [
            "I use a generic greeting like 'To whom it may concern'",
            "I research to find the name or use 'Dear Hiring Manager'",
            "I skip the greeting and start with the body of the letter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "What's Your Approach to Networking During the Job Search Process?",
        answer: "I strategically network with professionals in my field and ask for referrals",
        options: [
            "I reach out to as many people as possible, regardless of their relevance to my field",
            "I avoid networking; I prefer to apply to jobs independently",
            "I strategically network with professionals in my field and ask for referrals"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "How Do You Handle Salary Negotiations?",
        answer: "I do my research and come prepared with a reasonable range",
        options: [
            "I do my research and come prepared with a reasonable range",
            "I accept whatever is offered; I don't want to seem demanding",
            "I always ask for a much higher salary than I expect to get."
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "What Do You Do If You Haven’t Heard Back After an Interview?",
        answer: "I follow up with a polite email after a few weeks",
        options: [
            "I assume rejection and don't pursue it further",
            "I follow up with a polite email after a few weeks",
            "I keep sending emails until I get a response"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "What Do You Do if You Need to Reschedule an Interview?",
        answer: "I inform as soon as possible and request a new time respectfully",
        options: [
            "I cancel at the last minute; emergencies can't be helped",
            "I try to avoid rescheduling; it might look bad",
            "I inform as soon as possible and request a new time respectfully"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "How Do Your Certifications Contribute to Your Effectiveness in This Role?",
        answer: "They have provided me with specialized skills and knowledge relevant to this role",
        options: [
            "They have provided me with specialized skills and knowledge relevant to this role",
            "They don't really contribute much; I just completed them for my resume",
            "I'm not sure how they will be useful"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "What Motivated You to Pursue Your Specific Certifications?",
        answer: "I was motivated by the desire to deepen my expertise and stay updated in my field",
        options: [
            "I pursued them because they were easy to obtain",
            "I followed advice without much personal interest",
            "I was motivated by the desire to deepen my expertise and stay updated in my field"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "How Do You Stay Updated with Changes in Your Field?",
        answer: "I regularly participate in ongoing training, workshops, and read industry publications",
        options: [
            "I regularly participate in ongoing training, workshops, and read industry publications",
            "I occasionally read articles or watch videos online",
            "I rely on workplace training exclusively"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Are There Any Additional Certifications You Plan to Pursue?",
        answer: "Yes, I plan to pursue [specific certification] to further enhance my skills",
        options: [
            "I haven't thought about it",
            "Yes, I plan to pursue [specific certification] to further enhance my skills",
            "I don't think additional certifications are necessary"
        ]
    }
];
